PROFILE

I am a determined and goal-driven professional. I would describe myself as a friendly, approachable and highly motivated individual.

I adapt quickly to new environments and thrive on gaining new skills every time.

Every decision I make I keep the target audience at paramount importance, with effective data analysis and agile practices I thrive to create a better experience for clients.

I value others' opinions and like to learn in everything I do.

CONTACT

PHONE:

0413806543

WEBSITE:

www.zeebaig.net

EMAIL:

Baig.zee@hotmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/zee-baig

Address:

17 Constellation Street, Hallett Cove. SA 5158.

SKILLS

- SQL
- JavaScript
- Python
- Flask
- Express/Node JS
- React
- **Data Structures**
- Sass
- Git

VENDOR CERTIFICATIONS

- Prince2 Agile Practitioner
- Lean Six Sigma Black Belt

ZEESHAN BAIG

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

June 2023 Adelaide, AU

Software Engineering Immersive.

UNIVERSITY OF OXFORD

June 2017 Oxford, UK

Post Graduate Business Management Studies.

ANGLIA RUSKIN UNIVERSITY

Sept 2012 London, UK

Masters in Innovation.

UNIVERSITY OF KARACHI

June 2004 Karachi, Pak

Bachelors in Computer Science.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DP COMPUTING

Field Services Manager

Supported several IT projects for clients based on their business needs. Mostly we have been working with government departments, their database and

server management. Some of the clients we work with are, Federal courts, Tafe SA, Royal Adelaide Hospital, Adelaide Airport, Parafield Airport, Department of Defense, Coles group, Westpac Group, Woolworths group, National Heavy Vehicle Regulators, Aged care quality commission.

TARGET AUSTRALIA

July 2018 - Nov 2019

Dec 2019 to date

Store manager

Every decision I make I keep the target audience at the heart of everything we do, whilst working in different stores at Target Australia from underperforming stores to the launch of first online fulfillment center in SA, some of everyday work routine encompasses the following,

Managing online channel performance across the region to deliver smooth online sales operation, understand financials, analyze variances and initiate corrective actions.

Developing project related collateral including project briefs, presentations, complex data analysis, benefits trackers, fishbone diagrams, process maps, value stream maps and SOPs.

MARKS & SPENCER PIC UK

Oct 2010 – Jan 2018

Project Manager

I have managed different business units/projects within the company to increase the collective value of Marks & Spencer Plc in international market, whilst working at Marks and Spencer I have been highly regarded from higher management due to my consistent performance and achieving business targets effectively with high customer satisfaction. I have also been declared as "Probe Champion" due to effective probing skills. Worked as part of the lead team launching Marks & Spencer's bank and

engagement of retail customers about the latest business initiative.